# Michal Krawczyk

m www.linkedin.com/in/krawczykmichalmk/ www.michal-krawczyk.com

## **SUMMARY**

Transitioning from a successful career in engineering and customer service to frontend development, with a solid foundation in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python. A proactive learner with a technical mindset, keen to leverage my problem–solving skills to create intuitive user experiences. Excited about joining a forward–thinking company where I can contribute to meaningful projects and further develop my frontend skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Technican, Self-employed

TV Expert

January 2015 - December 2022, Dublin

· Facilitated CCTV installations, servicing, and installation of television systems, and troubleshooting WiFi/LAN issues.

#### SAT Engineer, SKY Ireland

Actavo

January 2015 - December 2021, Dublin

- · Conducted VIP and business customer servicing, along with special access installations using rope access.
- · Managed TV and broadband installations, provided onsite customer training, and resolved technical issues, improving overall customer satisfaction.

#### **Sales Assistant**

**Dunnes Stores** 

March 2008 - March 2015, Dublin

· Maintained high quality in-person customer service, managed stock levels, and ensured effective merchandising.

#### Technican

SAG II Sp. Z.o.o, Katowice

August 2004 - June 2007, Katowice, Poland

 $\cdot$  Handled construction part preparations, CNC machinery programming, and operations.

# **EDUCATION**

# **QQI 6 Digital Media Production**

Minor in Frontend Developer · CDETB · Dublin · 2024

#### **Bachelor Management and Marketing**

College of Occupational Safety, Poland  $\cdot$  Katowice, Poland  $\cdot$  2008

· Specialization: Psychology in Business

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

# MTA: Programming using JavaScript

Microsoft · 2022

# MTA: Programming using HTML and CSS

Microsoft · 2021

# **CCNA Routing & Switching**

Cisco Ireland · 2016

# **COURSEWORK**

#### **Full Stack Software Development**

Code Institute · 2022

# 1-1 Front-end Developer training with mentor

Devmentor.pl · 2021

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JAVASCRIPT(ES6), REACT, PYTHON, POSTGRESQL, GIT, GITHUB